const quiz2data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Guernica ___ by Pablo Picasso.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was painted", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "painted", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when we want to change the focus of the sentence. We are more interesting in the painting than the artist in this sentence."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Somebody ___ my car.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "has been stolen", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "has stolen ", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "When the subject performs the action of the verb, we use the active voice."
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "John stole money from his company and few days later he ___. ",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was arrested", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "arrested", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when who causes the action is obvious (the police in this sentence)."
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Most volcanoes eruptions ___ by tectonic plates moving towards each other, which usually produces violent eruptions.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "are caused ", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "caused", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when we are writing formal or scientific texts."
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "While I was sleeping, someone broke the window and stole my laptop.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When the subject performs the action of the verb, we use the active voice."
    },
    {
      id: 6, 
      question: "My office ____ every morning before start working.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is being cleaned", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "cleaned", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when we think who causes the action is not important or interesting."
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Gabriel José García Márquez ___ 'One Hundred Years of Solitude'.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "has been written", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "wrote", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "When the subject performs the action of the verb, we use the active voice."
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Highway 15 ____ due to a serious car accident.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "is closed", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "closed", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "The passive voice is often used to report something or to state a fact."
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "A lot of houses ____ in the storm.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "were destroyed", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "destroyed", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when we want to emphasize the receiver (houses) of the action."
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Last night someone ____ an accident and they closed the highway for 30 minutes.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "caused", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "was caused", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When the subject performs the action of the verb, we use the active voice."
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "Yogurt is a usually daily product made by bacterial fermentation of milk.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Active voice", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "Passive voice", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "The passive voice is used when we describe procedures or processes."
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "I ____ by how many people came to my concert.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "was surprised", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "surprised", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the passive voice when the subject is very long. It sounds more natural than: 'How many people came to my concert surprised me'."
    },
]

export default quiz2data